spillit.me 2013-06-23

# Spillit Privacy Policy

Last updated August 6th, 2012

## Your privacy is critically important to us. At Spillit we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We won't ask you for personal information unless we really need it.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our services.

It is Spillit's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please contact us via http://www.spillit.me/support 

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Spillit collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Spillit's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Spillit's visitors use Spillit. From time to time, Spillit may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Spillit also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Spillit does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Spillit choose to interact with Spillit in ways that require Spillit to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Spillit gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a website at Spillit to provide a birthday and email address. In each case, Spillit collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Spillit. Spillit does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Spillit may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to Spillit. For instance, Spillit may monitor the most popular pages on the Spillit site. Spillit may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Spillit does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Spillit discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Spillit's behalf or to provide services available at Spillit, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Spillit, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Spillit discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Spillit believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Spillit, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of Spillit and have supplied your email address, Spillit may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Spillit and our products.

Spillit takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Spillit uses cookies to help Spillit identify and track visitors, their usage of Spillit, and their website access preferences. Spillit visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Spillit, with the drawback that certain features of Spillit may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Privacy Policy for www.Spillit.me 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support@spillit.me. 

At www.Spillit.me, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.Spillit.me and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.Spillit.me makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.Spillit.me does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.Spillit.me.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.Spillit.me and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......   
Google Adsense   

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.Spillit.me send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.Spillit.me has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.Spillit.me's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

### Business Transfers

If Spillit, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Spillit goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Spillit may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Spillit may change Spillit's Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Spillit's sole discretion. Spillit encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Contact

If you have questions or complaints regarding our Data Use Policy or practices, please contact us through email at support@spillit.me. 

### Indemnification

The customer or website user agrees that he/she shall defend, indemnify, save and hold Best Interenet Guy LLC. harmless from any and all demands, liabilities, losses, costs and claims, including reasonable attorney's fees asserted against us, its agents, its customers, officers and employees, that may arise or result from any product, service or information provided. 

### Legal Jurisdiction

This policy is governed by the laws of the state of Oregon. Any disputes or other legal action taken against Spillit or Best Internet Guy LLC must take place in a federal or state court located in the state of Oregon. Users of Best Internet Guy LLC sites must first make a good faith effort to allow Best Internet Guy LLC to correct or remedy any conflicts/issues which may arise. If a conflict/issue does arise, you are required to notify Best Internet Guy LLC in writing, sent via certified mail, and include a full description of the issue, your proposed remedy, or remedies, for the issue, and sufficient time for Best Interner Guy LLC to fully review and resolve the issue to the mutual satisfaction of the parties involved.
